[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
It reminds me of my time at boot camp, too.
When I first went there,
everything was new, and everyone was picking a fight,
I was so scared.
You know, Yeom Il Hwan?
He looks scarier than Sergeant Kang Chan Seok.
Does he?
Yeah, I'm not joking.
Anyway, back then, Hyeon Uk was really nice to me.
[95th division training camp, a year ago]
[Yeom Il Hwan]
- Why? - Huh? It's nothing.
Hi.
Oh, hi!
Let's get along!
Yeah! Me too!
Is your name... Park Min Sik?
Oh.
No, it's Seok! Park Min Seok!
Oh, Min Seok.
Yeah.
I'm Kim Hyeon Uk.
Kim Hyeon Uk.
Good to meet you.
Good to meet you, too. Let's be nice to each other for the next five weeks.
Yeah, me too.
You know, drill instructors scared me.
When I first got here, they were so nice.
But once we got in here, they changed completely.
You there.
Shut up.
- Okay? - Sorry.
Did you see the drill instructor's washbasin earlier?
That was brutal.
I know. It's driving me nuts.
You.
Shut your mouth before I rip your tongue out, you hicks.
You hear me?
Do you?
- Huh? - You keep quiet.
Who the fuck is this now?
Do you want a go?
- Do you? - Go ahead.
- Shouldn't we stop them? - Just leave it.
Go ahead, fucker.
- Do you or not? - Bring it on.
Hey, there.
Hey.
Keep quiet.
[Kwon Tae Woong]
Trainees.
I don't want to hear your voices outside. Understood?
- Understood! - Understood!
The time is 17:27.
I'll inspect your belongings in ten minutes.
Anything you brought from outside is not allowed. Got it?
- Understood! - Understood!
I can't hear you. Got it?
Glasses and glasses cases are allowed.
Check if you've brought something unnecessary and you're still keeping it, especially,
if you've sneaked cigarettes and phones, this is your last chance.
There won't be a next time.
Understood?
- Understood! - Understood!
Let's get ready quickly.
Yeah.
When your packets arrive at your home,
[Episode 04: Trainee Kim Hyeon Uk] your parents will shed tears,
worrying whether you are doing fine and adapting well.
Then what will you tell them?
- We tell them we're doing great! - We tell them we're doing great!
You should write,
"Your brave son will become a soldier defending the country," right?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir.
I know some of you will write down song lyrics just because you don't know what to write.
Don't be unfilial. Behave, understood?
- Understood! - Understood, sir!
Trainee 4.
You don't have anything to tell your parents?
I don't.
Are you sure?
I am sure.
Is it really that hard to write to your parents who raised you and tell them you're doing well?
Are you really that ungrateful?
I am.
Min Seok.
Finish writing.
Dear my beloved parents,
Mom, Dad, are you well?
This is your only son, Min Seok.
After saying goodbye to you earlier today,
I just packed away the clothes and shoes I wore as a civilian.
It really hit me that I'm here in the army.
When you receive my clothes,
please don't cry.
I met a very nice guy who will be my battle buddy.
Tomorrow, I'll start my drills wearing a combat uniform.
I'll stay safe and become a true soldier.
So please, don't worry about me.
Mom, Dad,
I love you.
Everything's unfamiliar.
The place, the people, and the situation.
21 months ahead of me.
Can I really do this?
No, you got this, Park Min Seok.
I'm going to be reborn after this.
I'll do my best to become a better man...
Straighten your slippers.
Now, I'll teach you how to state your rank and name. Understood?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
- Louder! Understood? - Yes, sir!
In the military, when a superior calls you, you state your rank and name. What do you say?
- Rank and name, sir! - Rank and name, sir!
Rank and name. What do you say?
Hey.
Yes, sir?
Answer like that again, and you'll be shot on the spot. Got it?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
I can't hear you! Do you want to get smoked first? Got it?
Since you're still trainees without a rank,
you state your number instead of your rank. Got it?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
And you'll leave out "sir" at the end. Got it?
Hey.
Yes... Oh.
T-Trainee 12.
- Everyone, get in push-up position. - Push-up position!
Did I explain this two days ago?
- No, sir! - No, sir!
- I told you ten seconds ago. Am I right? - Yes, sir!
- Do you have the memory of a goldfish? - No, sir!
I'm going to give you another chance. Understood?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
- Up. - Up!
- Hey. - Trainee 12, Park Min Seok, sir.
You'll leave out "sir" at the end. Got it?
Who was that?
Who the hell just sighed?
Are you going to keep quiet?
Trainee 4, Yeom Il Hwan, sir.
Everyone, down.
- Push-up position! - Push-up position!
You don't deserve to learn.
- Understood? - Understood!
You will stay in this position until the end of training today.
- Got it? - Yes, sir!
- Louder. Got it? - Yes, sir!
Is he fucking stupid?
Fuck.
Can you keep quiet?
What the fuck did you say?
You're not the only one getting smoked. It's hard for everyone.
What the fuck are you talking about?
What did you say?
Hey.
Say that again.
- What? - You fucking bastard.
You fucking bastard!
Hey, hey, stop.
Fuck you.
Stop him!
Go on, bastard.
Hey, stop.
Stop him.
What the heck are you doing?
Number 9.
Trainee 9, Kwon Tae Woong.
Number 4.
Trainee 4, Yeom Il Hwan, sir.
Follow me.
Yes, sir!
Oh, gosh.
We're fucked. So fucked.
We're getting smoked again because of that crazy dude.
Hey, we should probably stay quiet.
What kind of bullshit is this?
It's alright.
Nothing to worry about.
You must have relied on each other.
Yes, we have, back then.
And now?
Are you...
Oh, no.
We still get along well.
I should be nice to Hyeon Uk from now on.
- Yes. - Right.
What ramen should I eat later?
Well...
Corporal Park Min Seok.
Perhaps...
No, it's nothing.
Well, okay.
Let's stay sharp on watch.
Yes, sir.
Look at you, short-timers. You're all here on time without your morning smoke?
Sir, we always come out when we're supposed to. It's just this shit that won't come out!
I got constipated here, of all places. I didn't even get it in boot camp.
Hey, just hold out till we get Army burgers!
They'll clear you right up.
There. Jeon Se Gye.
Private First Class Jeon Se Gye.
Didn't you shoot a commercial before you came here?
Yes, sir!
"If you're constipated...
Mayday."
Nice.
Everyone, about face!
Give me a loud five-second shout!
Okay, okay.
Everyone, about face!
Wow, is this the power of quitting smoking?
Your voices sound so clear!
Now that you all quit smoking and got healthy,
I'll let you skip the morning run...
Actually, no! Guide on Kim Sang Hun!
Sergeant Kim Sang Hun, guide!
Form up! Hurry up! Hurry!
- One, two, hup! - One, two, hup!
Chungseong!
Chungseong.
Is roll call over?
I came out early so I could run with the guys from Second Company.
No, sir. We were just forming up for a run.
Then that's good.
Let's run together.
Run. Let's go.
Second Company!
The cadence is "A Fine Man!"
Cadence start!
One, two, three, four!
♪ A fine man ♪
♪ Out of many ♪
♪ I am the man ♪
♪ A fine man I am ♪
Hey, Min Seok.
You run better than I expected.
Corporal Park Min Seok!
Yes, sir, my stamina has increased since becoming a corporal, sir!
Watch out for injuries, have a safe run!
Yes, sir, thank you!
- Good! - ♪ A fine man ♪
- Company Commander. - Yes, sir.
Make sure these kids get enough breakfast.
They have civilian support duties at Yooncheon-ri today.
But sir, it's the weekend. Isn't it too sudden?
There are no "weekends" for operations, nor do they come announced.
Understood, sir.
The mayor will be there...
The press has their eyes on it, too.
I'd like our Second Company to make an appearance there.
I'm sure you understand me.
Yes, sir.
Perfect. I expect no less from you.
- Yes, sir. Chungseong. - ♪ A fine man ♪
♪ Out of many ♪
Our battalion commander's stamina is seriously impressive!
I shouldn't have to go through this, I'm a short-timer!
But, still...
I think it's good exercise.
Good? What's good about this?
Well, I have to admit, it is refreshing.
Weekend mornings aren't supposed to be this tiring!
This is the admin office speaking.
There is a civilian support mission scheduled for today at Yooncheon-ri.
All personnel in the Second Company, without exception...
- What? - must gather at the parade grounds by 9:00.
A civil support mission?
Did I just hear that correctly?
Yes, they said "civilian support mission," loud and clear.
But it's so sudden!
This is so unfair, it's the weekend.
This is unheard of, isn't it?
Damn it, why did it have to be our company?
Maybe the beef between the company commander and the battalion commander?
And why did I have to get so unlucky in my last year of service?
This sucks!
- Come on, just hurry up and get ready. - Yes, sir!
Get everyone ready, Min Seok.
Got it, sir.
Hey, Bit Na Ri, and Hyeon Uk.
Keep your guards up even higher out there, got it?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
- Hurry up. - Yes, sir.
This is the admin office again.
Under the battalion commander's orders,
all personnel must change into their Class A uniform.
I will repeat this one more time.
Under the battalion commander's orders,
- all personnel must wear the Class A uniform. - What?
Why would we need to wear that for a civil support mission?
My exact question, too.
If we end up going shoveling or something, it's only going to ruin the uniform...
- Wait a minute. - What if, by any chance...
we got invited to the town festival?
- Makgeolli? - Oh, makgeolli!
- Makgeolli? - Makgeolli?
- Quick, get changed! - Yes, sir!
Maybe we're going to some municipal event!
If so...
there may just be some pretty college girl volunteers there as well!
- College girls? - Oh, yes!
Those pretty college girl volunteers...
Hey, Bit Na Ri. Come over here.
Well, just imagine them seeing us and going... "Oh, Mr. Soldier!
Thank you for your service!"
And then...
She hands you a vitamin drink...
But then... Your hand brushes against hers...
"Ohoho!"
She giggles, all shy and flustered, and...
"Oh..."
"What strong hands you have!"
And straight to day one it is!
Corporal Im Da Hye, may I borrow some sunscreen?
No way. You need to become a corporal first.
Yes, sir...
Hey, Bit Na Ri.
Here you go.
Private First Class Moon Bit Na Ri! Thank you, sir!
- Go easy on it, okay? - Yes, sir!
This is the company commander speaking.
Private First Class Jeon Se Gye and Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
Report to the company commander's office. Over.
- Quick, change and get going! - Yes, sir.
Yes?
Chungseong! Love you!
Private First Class Jeon Se Gye and one other,
- reporting to the company commander's office! - Good.
- Jeon Se Gye. - Private First Class Jeon Se Gye.
I summoned you, Se Gye and Hyeon Uk,
to tell you that you two will be staying here.
I'll inform your squad leaders.
The battalion commander is worried that people may take photos of you.
He wants you to stay behind.
- Is that, sir? - Se Gye.
Private First Class Jeon Se Gye.
You are Jeon Se Gye.
But, Company Commander, sir...
Not a lot of people recognize me anymore, sir.
- Not even people from other Companies do. - That's precisely why.
We don't want gossip that you've changed, much less with photo evidence, too.
Oh, dear.
But, sir, it can't be that bad!
Oh, calm down. I was just joking.
I'm so hurt I'm on the verge of tears, see?
Right here, do you see it, sir?
Alright, alright. Hey, Hyeon Uk.
Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
It hasn't been long since you were assigned, and your priority is to get used to your unit.
- So stay behind, alright? - Yes, sir!
- But don't take this as a vacation. - Yes, sir!
Good.
Okay, let's go.
If it were up to me, I'd rather do civilian support.
Working with the first sergeant is...
What are you talking about?
I'm wonderful to work with!
Hey! I'll buy you a Buddion.
Private First Class Jeon Se Gye, thank you, sir!
We'll be back.
Oh, A-class! Are you going on vacation?
Watch and learn, nerds! This is what it means to be a cool guy!
So, where are we going today, sir?
I don't know, but anywhere would be better than here!
- That's true, sir! - And there'll be college girls, no?
I'm so excited.
I have a feeling I might get a girlfriend today!
I'm excited to taste some real food for once!
To the flowery meadows, my fellow honeybees!
- Buzz, buzz! - Buzz!
- Let's go, baby! - Buzz, buzz!
What the heck.
What's this?
This is just a plain old flood damage restoration site.
So why did we have to dress up for this?
Perfect weather for manual labor.
Chungseong! Love you!
- Love you. - Chungseong, love you.
Yeah.
Hey. Dressed up in A-class, huh? Are you going on vacation?
Oh, stop making fun of us, sir.
We used a lot of softener for these.
So why are we wearing these, anyway?
This wouldn't be an army if I told you, now would it?
You just do what you're told to.
Everyone, gather up. Let's take a group photo.
What group photo, now, sir?
All your mothers and girlfriends will see it.
Come on, hurry up.
Yes, sir.
What did I just say? It's for your moms!
Smile!
Hey, Kang Chan Seok, your face...
- Oh. That's your relaxed face, huh. - Yes, sir.
Hey, I said smile!
Good. On three.
One, two, three!
One more time. Two, three...
Okay. We'll take 7 and 8 later.
- Yes, sir! - Okay. Eyes on me.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
You see all that debris behind me?
We're here to restore the flood damage.
We've got lots of eyes on us, boys.
Let's focus and get this done, and get back home as quickly as possible.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
- Jong Uk. - Corporal Cha Jong Uk.
Get the boys to hand out work gloves.
- Yes, sir. - Go, go!
- Yes, sir. - Going, sir.
- Ugh, makgeolli... - I want makgeolli...
Hey, Hyeon Uk, put your gloves on. You'll get hurt.
- As for me, I just prefer my bare hands. - Yes, sir.
I don't know why we don't throw this thing out.
The army sucks.
- Let's take a short break. - Yes, sir.
You work so hard, sir, even during the weekend.
Oh, but it's not just me. You're working, too.
Let's enjoy this break and get back to it.
Yes, sir!
What is it?
I sense you've got something to say.
It's okay, you can tell me.
It's just...
Well, Private Jeon Se Gye...
Seeing that you're a celebrity,
it wouldn't be strange for you to want some kind of special treatment.
Special treatment, huh.
There's no such thing in the army.
We're all soldiers, and nothing more.
It sure seems like that isn't always the case.
Oh? Really?
Like who, for example?
Oh, well...
This isn't specifically about him, but...
Last time, when I misfired a blank,
if it was anyone other than Corporal Park Min Seok who was with me...
I can't help but wonder if it still would've blown over so easily.
So you're wondering if you got off easy because he's the division commander's son?
Is that what you mean?
Well, not in particular, sir.
- I was just giving an example. - Well, that "special treatment..."
It's not always a good thing. Sometimes it can get in your way.
- Even if it is special? - Of course.
Especially when...
It wasn't even wanted.
It's just worse.
- Is that right? - Yeah.
- Come on, let's get this over with. - Yes, sir!
What's wrong?
Let me guess. You're wondering why we put in all this effort when there's no one around?
That's correct, sir.
It doesn't matter if there's anyone around or not, does it?
You're just supposed to do your best on the task at hand.
I'm surprised to hear that from a celebrity.
Hey, I may be a celebrity in the outside world,
but here, we're all the same. Just soldiers.
It's just that I'm a little...
No, more than a little, dare I say, very...
handsome soldier.
You're right, sir!
W-wait a second.
[Buddion]
I noticed the poor thing, stuck there all alone.
- Do you want it? - I'm all right, sir!
- No, take it. - It's seriously alright, sir.
- You mean that? - Yes, sir.
Oh, I'm getting a signal right away.
I need to use the restroom.
Yes, sir.
Why don't you come with me? You haven't gone even once.
I'm good, sir!
You sure? Alright then, I'll be back.
Yes, sir!
- What are you doing? - I'm fine, sir.
See the bucket there?
- Hey, stop! Stop. - Stop.
Good.
Okay, smile!
Okay.
One, two, three.
Smile. With your teeth.
- Yes, sir. - Wipe away a little sweat.
Okay, okay.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Hey, come here.
Look at you sweating.
What's keeping you? Come over here.
Sorry, sir.
Watch out.
Nice, nice.
[Cyber Knowledge Information Room]
You're back, sir.
Let's get it done quickly and go to the post exchange.
Sounds great, sir.
Private First Class Jeon Se Gye. May I use the restroom?
Sure, go ahead.
Thank you, sir.
We're almost done. Cheer up.
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
Hey, sweep there properly.
Yes, sir.
- Don't sweep this way. - Fine.
At ease!
Company, attention!
Chungseong! Love you!
Chungseong. Love you.
At ease.
At ease!
- Do what you were doing. - Yes, sir!
Corporal Park Min Seok.
- You're working hard. - It's nothing, sir. Thank you, sir.
Reporters, please feel free to interview them from now on.
I'd appreciate it if you could give us some good coverage.
Please come this way.
Did you all enjoy breakfast?
Corporal Cha Jong Uk. Yes, we did, sir.
What's the most important thing when we work?
It's being safe.
Yes, sir.
Sang Hun, here.
- Second Company, attention! - Attention.
- Attention! - Attention!
I appreciate your hard work in this heat.
What we are doing here is
helping heal the hearts of the people of Yooncheon-ri, devastated by the flood.
But...
why do you think I, your battalion commander,
ordered you to wear your Class A uniforms in this mud?
Well...
Private First Class Moon Bit Na Ri.
What do you think the reason is?
Because they are clean, sir!
Come on.
Yes, that's not wrong.
If we wear fatigues,
that means we're just here to lend a hand.
But when we stand here in these spotless uniforms,
that means
we are here as the very safety our country has promised.
Right now,
you are the finest Class A rescue force
our country has sent!
Do you understand?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
Alright, let's keep it up!
Back to your position!
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
Our battalion commander is awesome.
Class A.
Rescue force.
I almost cried.
Let's get to work.
- Yes, sir! - Sorry, sir!
Have you had breakfast?
- Yes, we have, sir. - Yes, we have, sir.
Alright, stay safe.
You're here, Baek Ho. Chungseong!
Oh, chief. Chungseong.
I haven't seen you in a while, and you've gotten so thin!
What are you talking about? I gained weight.
You did?
Hello, sir. I'm sorry I didn't get a chance to introduce myself sooner.
I'm Lieutenant Colonel Byeon Hyeok Jin, newly assigned here.
What? You look younger than Baek Ho, and you're already a lieutenant colonel?
Oh, not at all.
What have you been doing so far, not getting promoted?
I didn't have time to get promoted because I was busy taking care of you, chief.
That's nonsense.
Corporal No Hee Jeong. We have a big problem.
I'm going to kill you for real this time if it's not a big deal.
I mean it. This is a huge problem.
What is it?
Damn it. It is huge.
What should we do?
Communication security. Corporal No Hee Jeong speaking.
Communication security. Corporal Sung Yoon Mo speaking.
- I'll check that for you. - How may I assist you?
Copy. Chungseong!
Communication security. Corporal No Hee Jeong speaking.
Hey, what's up?
Chungseong, Battalion Commander...
What is it?
Someone posted on the base forum
[Shinhwa Unit Is Covering Up a Shooting!] that our battalion covered up a shooting.
We're getting calls from everywhere. It's chaos.
[Measures against the false accusation online] He's on civilian support duty now.
[All commanders exercise extra caution] I'll get back to you, sir.
Please hold for a second.
Communication security. Corporal Sung Yoon Mo speaking.
Communication security. Corporal No Hee Jeong speaking.
Yes, he's out on duty.
Damn it.
Hang up for now.
[Regimental Commander Kwon Sang Guk]
- Chungseong. - You, bastard.
- What the fuck are you doing? - I'm sorry, sir.
Get your ass to regimental headquarters right now!
Yes, sir. Chung--
- Second Company Commander. - Yes.
Something came up, so I should head back now.
Can you wrap it up here?
Yes, sir. If you don't mind...
Did something happen?
Well, I'll tell you when you finish here and get back to base.
Yes, sir. Chungseong.
Open it.
Take it easy.
I'll throw it away.
Next.
You're spilling it all.
It's going everywhere.
- Hey. - Yes?
You're way stronger than you look.
Thank you, ma'am.
Let's go.
Go where?
The wall around my house completely collapsed.
Can you mend it?
It looks like the whole place is about to wash away!
Ma'am, I am sorry, but I'm on duty here.
Is that so?
Well, then, it can't be helped.
I'll do it on my own.
I might end up crushed under a rock.
- You can come get my body then. - No...
When the soul's gone, the body will be light as a feather.
- It'll be easy to clean up. - Ma'am...
It's not like that, ma'am...
First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin.
The key to civilian support is responding to the needs on the ground.
Go help the lady.
Yes, sir!
Huh?
As a Class A rescue force,
I, First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin, will return after fixing her wall--
- Got it, on your way. - Yes, yes.
- Chungseong! I will... - Let's go.
- Thank you. - Of course.
Take good care of her.
Be careful, ma'am.
- Waste no time. Take good care of her. - You got this!
Safe way there.
Good luck.
My, she came all the way down here.
Who is she?
She lives on the hillside over there.
She does that to every young man she sees.
Is there a story behind this?
The thing is, she...
[Report on malicious post regarding the camp]
[Online circulation status / Background]
[A post titled "Shinhwa Unit Covering Up a Shooting" began circulating online]
Regimental Commander, this was not a shooting.
During a safety inspection after returning to the post,
a minor accidental discharge of a blank round occurred.
Does it matter if it's a live round or a blank?
To civilians,
fire coming out of a gun means a shooting!
And once you say "cover-up,"
the media will come running. Got it?
I'm sorry, sir.
I'll get this resolved as quickly as possible. I'll take care of it.
You know what will happen if it goes out of control?
I do, sir.
Write the incident report for Division Headquarters yourself and bring it to me by tomorrow.
Get out!
Yes, sir.
Chungseong.
[Press vehicle]
Guard Commander. Why is MBS here?
That's what I'm saying.
[May this youth shine for the motherland!] What would they be here for?
Did something happen to Jeon Se Gye?
Maybe they're here for an interview.
Should I go and ask them?
- Hang on a second. - If we could enter...
Communication security. Chungseong. Staff Sergeant Oh Se Ho, Guard Commander.
MBS is at the main gate right now.
What are they here for?
[Defense Daily Reporter Yoon]
[Regimental Commander's Office]
Oh, Mr. Yoon!
I was meaning to talk to you.
You called me because of that post on the base forum?
You always get the news fast.
You know what, how about we meet in person and have a talk?
Did a wild boar ram into it?
- Ma'am. - Yes?
Even as an elite soldier in the top 10%, no, 5% in terms of combat and physical ability,
this is more than I can handle on my own...
If you can't do it, forget it.
I could try moving those heavy rocks alone,
even though I might break my back.
I could die from that, but that's okay.
- That's not what I'm saying. - It's not like I have anything else to do.
I might as well die.
No, no, ma'am.
I'll do it. I can do it.
Come on, put some muscle into it!
What's wrong with you? Oh, you are weaker than I thought.
You put it there earlier.
Look, it doesn't fit.
- It... - It needs to be a tight fit.
But ma'am, it'll take longer to find one that fits perfectly.
Don't you talk back to me, young man.
Sorry, ma'am.
You're being too slow!
I don't want to do this anymore.
Good job, there you go.
Oh, goodness gracious!
Well, aren't you clumsy!
I thought they fed their soldiers well in the army these days,
so why are you so weak?
Are they starving you or something?
I'm getting lightheaded...
Look, it's sticking out right there!
It'll collapse if you do it like that!
- My hemoglobin is spiking-- - Don't talk back.
Just do it.
My task ends at stacking these back up again...
- But never mind, anything else, ma'am? - What?
- Here, these, too. - Okay.
Hey, hey, hey!
That's my darn cane!
- I'm sorry, ma'am. - Yes, yes. Whatever.
What difference is there between this and constructing a fort in the mountains, huh?
I thought you said "outside air" is healing on its own?
Have fun breathing.
Hey, you.
Shut up and hurry up.
I want to go back fast.
Yes, sir.
Always hounding on me...
What are you doing?
It's not even that heavy.
- Oh, no! - Deary me!
Oh, what a disaster!
- I'm so sorry, ma'am! - The whole year's worth of efforts, gone!
Why are you fondling it? Just leave the damn thing alone!
- But it's such a waste! - Hey, prick!
Get down here and change.
We still have lots of work to get through.
What a mess you've made, you idiot.
But I don't have anything to change into.
Who cares? Get back down here right now!
Hey, make sure the chickens are comfortable enough.
Make it soft and cushioned, okay? Spread it out evenly.
- Soft and cushioned... - Yes, evenly.
Hey, could you step out of the way?
They're breeding hens.
Very valuable, alright? They need good care.
Ah, yes, ma'am.
Oh, my. It's just a chicken. Nothing to be scared of.
Go, get out!
What kind of a soldier gets so scared of a chicken?
The chicken's feet are too big!
What are you even talking about?
You're such a funny guy.
They're making weird noises.
Hey.
Come over here.
Yes?
Come take a look at the light here in the kitchen.
It flickered for a few minutes, and then it turned off.
The light?
Yes.
First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin. I'll fix it up right away for you.
What is it? Are you going to fix it or not?
What are you doing, just looking at it?
Ma'am.
- This is more than just changing the bulb. - What?
The electrical system in this house is estimated to date back to the 1960s or 1970s.
The copper in the wiring has oxidized, significantly reducing its conductivity.
In addition, worn-out insulation and sheathing could cause electrical leakage at any time.
What the hell are you babbling about?
I'm saying it's dangerous.
And it's very dangerous.
If I were to come into direct contact with this exposed wire,
my body would become a conductor connected to the ground--
Shut it!
Leave it if you can't do it.
Even if something goes wrong, I'll just get electrocuted and die, won't I?
- Right? - No...
With someone here to haul my body away, I feel like I'm in good hands.
My body will go stiff when I get electrocuted, so it will be easy to move.
Must be nice and easy to put in a coffin, too.
Ma'am, why do you keep saying such things?
Fine, I'll do it.
I studied humanities...
- What? - It's nothing.
- Oh? - Oh, ma'am.
I think I can do this. I found what caused the problem.
If you put them together...
What was that noise?
What was that? Was that a water deer?
Wasn't it more like a scream?
You're just imagining it.
Well, you did a good job today.
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you, sir.
- You guys must be hungry. - Yes, sir!
It's about time.
I'm starving. What's for dinner today?
Stir-fried sausages and vegetables, seaweed soup, and seasoned laver...
Delivery!
Delivery?
Did anyone order jjajangmyeon here?
- What? - That sounds yummy.
Did anyone order jjajangmyeon?
Here.
Oh?
What?
- Is this for real? - Wow!
Calm down, calm down.
You deserve this for your hard work.
- Am I right? - Yes, sir!
Company, attention!
To our gracious, merciful, handsome, and magnificent company commander, salute!
- Chungseong! Love you! - Chungseong! Love you!
Chungseong. Love you.
They're all large portions.
Fried dumplings are on the house!
You silly bastards.
- Salute! - Chungseong! Love you!
I'm sorry about these guys.
Get one each.
Pass it back.
To the back.
Slow down, you'll choke.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Why are you not eating?
Private First Class Moon Bit Na Ri.
I already finished it.
You're number one in the company at this.
Thank you, sir!
Do you want more?
U-Uh, no, sir!
No? I was going to share with you if you wanted.
In fact, I do, sir.
Then you should have said that. Here.
Private First Class Moon Bit Na Ri. Thank you, sir!
Company Commander, I love you!
Sure. Take your time.
Yes, sir.
Can I have a bite?
- Yes, sir. - Thank you.
Bro.
When we finish this jjajangmyeon, we'll crave a cigarette badly, won't we?
I wasn't thinking about it.
You just made me think of it.
I feel so empty.
- Oh, right. - Yummy.
- Pass this back. - Yes, sir.
Pass along.
It's good.
Don't forget to drink water.
Thank you, sir.
What's with the sudden volunteer work?
Enjoy while you can.
You, too.
- Corporal Cha Byeong Ho. - Alright.
- Private First Class Moon Bit Na Ri. - Yes, Na Ri.
You too.
Thank you, sir.
- Sergeant Kim Sang Hun. Thank you, sir. - Thank you, sir.
- You too, Da Hye. - Corporal Im Da Hye.
There you go.
How sweet.
Attention while seated!
To our gracious, merciful, handsome, and magnificent company commander, salute!
- Chungseong! Love you! - Chungseong! Love you!
Chungseong. Love you.
You silly guys. Stop it now!
Here, pour for yourself.
Yes, First Sergeant.
Is something going on at the unit?
Sorry?
Did you fix it, ma'am?
I flipped the breaker, you idiot!
What kind of man can't even handle a little electrical work?
You knocked out the power to the whole house.
Then you just flopped down to take a break.
Must be comfortable.
Ma'am...
Electricity is like an invisible enemy.
The wiring in this traditional house uses outdated standards from the 1960s and 1970s.
Its insulation resistance is dangerously low, with a high risk of fire and electric shock.
Next time you need to fix a light, call a professional--
Shut it already.
Shut up and eat this so you feel better.
When did you make this?
The power wasn't even on.
I can make this even with my eyes closed.
Eat up.
You need to feel better to move the rocks.
- I thought I moved all the rocks earlier-- - What?
Nothing, ma'am.
Oh, but this looks like a lot.
I've been watching my diet lately. If I eat all this, my blood sugar will...
Thank you for preparing it.
Wow.
It looks yummy, very hearty...
Are you not eating?
No, I just prepare food like this every day.
Go ahead and eat.
Yes, ma'am.
It's a little too strong for me, though.
- Strong? - No.
- Too strong? - No, it's not.
My family usually seasons food pretty heavily at home, too.
Thank you for the food.
Oh, my.
You cleaned your bowl without leaving a drop of sauce!
Here, eat some more.
No, ma'am, hold on a second.
I'm already full.
If you don't want it, it's fine.
I can just throw it all away.
No, don't! I'll eat.
Will you?
Thank you.
Wow.
It looks yummier, heartier...
Who is that?
Doesn't he look good?
It's my youngest son.
Oh, my.
Dear.
He used to like noodles a lot.
I didn't know you had a son.
It might have been better if you asked your son to change the light bulb...
Oh, then this must be for your son, too.
It gets lonely, so I always set the table for both of us.
But noodles will get soggy. It's better to cook when he's here.
Soggy or not, it doesn't matter.
He can't eat it anyway.
Your son...
He's probably somewhere far away.
Maybe somewhere in the sky.
Maybe she brought me here because I reminded her of her son.
Well, you reminded me of my son.
This rascal...
He used to love noodles.
Ma'am.
Is it okay if I eat this too?
Sure, go ahead.
My little Chang Ju...
You must be full.
Someone's here to enjoy it for you.
It's really good.
These are the best noodles I've ever had.
Oh, you're someone's precious boy, too...
There.
My, look at this.
I should wash it.
Oh my.
Looks good.
Dry already, will you?
There you go.
Looks good.
[Oh Seok Jin]
I'm so sorry, ma'am.
The wall is collapsing...
Look at that prick.
You dummy!
What are you doing in there? Get yourself out already!
How did it get this late already?
Seok Jin, we couldn't reach you, so we're heading back first.
Take your time helping the old lady, then come back.
Oh, ma'am...
Thank you.
Oh, it's cold.
They aren't dry yet.
What was that?
I thought the lady wasn't here.
Who are you?
G-G-Ghost!
Mom! Mom?
He passed out!
My, this soldier passes out at the drop of a hat.
The dead son from the picture...
What?
What on earth did you tell him that he thinks I'm dead?
You said he was somewhere in the sky...
I did. He was in the sky.
My son is a pilot. A captain.
Did you say you came from the US today?
- Yes, and I came straight here. - Yes.
I can't come here very often.
So she gets lonely.
Whenever she sees a man in uniform,
she thinks of me and goes out of her way to take care of them.
Thanks to this young soldier today,
I got my house all fixed up.
It was so nice having someone around in my house again after so long.
Was it?
Yes.
First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin?
Thank you.
Seeing my mother smile like that again is such a relief.
Then I feel relieved, too. I feel like I've done my part.
Yes.
Take this.
It's mugwort rice cakes.
Take it to the camp and share it with other soldiers.
Even with my bad back, I went out and picked mugwort to make these rice cakes.
They should be good.
How could I accept something this precious...
Thank you. I'll enjoy this.
I'm sorry, you know, for everything.
I just know today was hard for you. I made you work so hard.
I'm sorry.
My son, you see, he's busy all the time.
Even on these rare occasions when he comes by to visit,
there's never enough time to get a good look at his face.
But anyway...
Mr. Soldier...
I actually had a great time just bickering with you all day.
It was so much fun!
Oh, thank you.
Treat him well, okay?
- Yes, Mother. - Good.
- Ma'am. - Yes?
I have to admit...
I had a lot of fun today, too.
Chungseong!
Oh, yeah, right.
First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin!
Reporting in after a very successful civilian support mission!
Chungseong!
- Love you! - Alright.
- Ma'am! - Yes?
I wish you good health.
Okay, okay.
You did a good job today.
- Mr. Soldier. - Oh, it's nothing.
Go on, go.
- Alright, ma'am. I'll be going now. - Yes.
Goodbye.
Hey.
Come by anytime you're craving some noodles!
Yes, ma'am!
Bye!
Oh, one second, please.
What is it?
- Ma'am! - What? Why? What is it?
- What's the matter? - I...
I need to use the toilet.
What?
Over there.
- It's right over there. - Oh, okay.
Thank you, ma'am. That was a lot of noodles, if you get me.
Oh, you rotten bastard.
Communication security, Corporal No Hee Jeong speaking.
- Well, that's... - Oh, he hasn't come back yet.
- We'll report back as soon as he does. - As soon as he's back.
Yes, chungseong, sir!
Communication security, Corporal No Hee Jeong speaking.
Oh, we haven't been able to confirm that yet.
Communication security, this is the Second Company admin office.
- What can I help you with? - I have no idea, sir.
We're not sure yet...
Are you a journalist?
I'm not sure.
What? My name?
Hey, idiot! Why are you speaking to a journalist?
Hang up on him. Come on!
Y-yes, sir, I'll call you back right away...
Explain what's going on.
Communication security, this is the Second Company admin office.
What can I help you with...
First Sergeant...
It's that reporter again, from just now...
Mom! It's me!
I'm fine!
Yeah?
What shooting accident?
What are you even talking about?
There was no accident.
Nothing happened. Don't worry.
Yeah. Alright.
A shooting? No way.
Chungseong! Love you!
One moment, coming through!
- Good work. - Great work, everyone.
- Did something happen? - What the heck, that scared me.
What's he going to do now?
He was supervising, right?
Wow. He's totally screwed.
What was that?
Hey, Yoon Mo.
Corporal Sung Yoon Mo!
What's going on? Did something happen?
Well... It's...
Corporal Park Min Seok...
Huh?
It's...
Someone posted something on the forum...
- Forum? - Yes, sir, that's right.
Great job, sir!
- You too. - Thank you, sir!
What did you do all day?
I was with Private First Class Jeon Se Gye, and cleaned the quarters, sir!
Did you hear anything unusual?
Well, what do you mean, sir?
Sergeant Kim Sang Hun.
I need to go speak with Hyeon Uk in private, outside.
Okay. Go ahead.
Thank you, sir.
Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
I'll be right back, sir.
Think it'll be alright, sir?
It's no surprise that Min Seok would assume so.
I knew this would happen ever since they made that forum.
Security is key in the army, right?
So how would a forum be a good idea in the first place?
Keep an eye on those two.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Hyeon Uk.
Just use your words and say it to my face.
Don't go doing this behind my back.
I don't know what you mean.
I know it's you.
You wrote that post, didn't you?
About the blank shooting accident.
You really want to dig it back up and screw me over?
Is that why you did this?
You were the only one who stayed behind today. Who else can it possibly be?
Did you just sigh at me?
Sir, today...
I was with Private First Class Jeon Se Gye the entire day.
You...
If it isn't you...
If it's not...
- I'm going to, I swear I'll... - What are you going to do, then?
You'll just kick me out again, huh?
What?
It's nothing, sir.
Whatever I do...
It doesn't even matter.
I'm the one who loses every time.
"Every time?"
Corporal Park Min Seok.
I'm just going to head inside.
What do you mean by "lose?"
What do you...
The reason why I couldn't tell you what was going on right away...
was because of the other soldiers there.
I didn't want to cause a scene.
- I hope you understand. - Of course, sir.
I took the post down as soon as I got back,
but it seems it has already made its way around through various forums.
[Report on malicious posts regarding the camp]
I managed to keep the news from being spread through some journalists I know, but...
The problem is...
The higher-ups have noticed that something is wrong.
[It's serious if it's real] And I checked the IP address, too.
The post was made on the camp grounds.
[Is this the truth about Shinhwa Unit?]
[They covered up a shooting accident...] Request the military investigation agency
[for a battalion commander's promotion.] for a history log
of this post through the camp network.
Let's get this guy, quick.
Got something to say?
No, sir...
But if I may,
I would like to share my opinion, sir.
Sure, go on ahead.
Well, I've been thinking...
But I'm not sure if the poster is in the wrong,
or...
If the person responsible for the issue being discussed is the wrong one.
I haven't made up my mind,
so I haven't been able to request an investigation yet, sir.
So what you're saying is,
the source of the problem must be the commander who made a forum in the first place?
Is that correct?
Second Company Commander.
Do you remember what I told you before?
Yes, sir.
If we punish a soldier, it's a sign that our unit has fallen behind.
The higher-ups should take responsibility.
The commanders should take responsibility.
So...
I'm going to take responsibility.
It was my order.
Yet you want to be held responsible for it?
It happened in the Second Company.
Moreover...
I am the commander of the Second Company.
We're in the middle of a promotion evaluation.
Are you sure about this?
Yes, sir. I'm sure.
[Company Commander, Captain Cho Baek Ho]
[Shinhwa Second Company Order of Battle]
Come in.
First Sergeant! What are you doing here at this hour?
Oh, I figured you might be having a rough time.
So I decided to drop by in case you haven't gone home yet.
Don't tell me you're empty-handed.
No way.
Ta-da.
Come with me.
It looks so good!
- Go on, dig in. - Yes.
Oh, right. I heard that the battalion commander rushed to the division headquarters earlier.
Well, that was fast.
Did something happen between the two of you?
Nothing big, really.
I just had a talk with him.
I told him I'd take full responsibility.
What?
Oh, no, there's no need for you to do that.
It'll all blow over soon if you just keep quiet and wait.
I'm just not made for it, I guess.
Keeping quiet, waiting for something to pass...
It's promotion evaluation season, though...
This is just how it's destined to be. I've come to terms with it.
That is some cruel destiny, no doubt about it.
You can say that again, sir.
Seems I'll be decommissioned sooner than I anticipated!
I want to laugh with you, I do,
but I can't bring myself to.
I just know you haven't eaten anything today.
Go on, eat up.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
I'd never let your kindness go to waste, sir.
This tteokbokki is so good.
Tteokbokki tastes best when you get it for me, sir.
From now on...
T-Try some of those fried sides, too.
It's fresh out of the fryer. I'm sure it's delicious.
All this time...
Thank you for everything, First Sergeant.
Really,
if it weren't for you...
I would've...
Oh, stop! Get back to eating your tteokbokki.
Go on, eat, eat!
No, sir. What I meant was,
I would've missed out on this amazing tteokbokki if it weren't for you!
Oh, you silly goose.
Wow, it's just so good.
I really appreciate this, sir.
It doesn't even matter.
I'm the one who loses every time.
Chungseong, love you.
Oh, hi, Se Gye.
Can't sleep, sir?
Yeah, I couldn't fall asleep.
You did a good job today.
Thank you.
Enjoy your ramen.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Sir?
Corporal Park Min Seok.
Yes?
I have something I need to tell you, sir.
What is it?
Excuse me.
Are you sure about that?
Yes, sir.
Hey, it's me.
Want to hear something funny as hell?
We've got Park Min Seok here.
Yeah, that idiot, you remember?
Oh, dear Min Seok...
What's going on now?
About Hyeon Uk, sir...
Is he okay?
It's only natural if you're nervous.
I did the same thing as a private.
He's new here.
How did that get there?
I was with Private First Class Jeon Se Gye the entire day.
- You're back, sir! - Yeah.
May I use the restroom, sir?
It's hot...
Hey, you.
What's your problem?
Why are you doing this to me? Why?
What are you doing, sir?
You little piece of...
See me outside. Quietly.
Why can't we just talk here?
What?
Well, Corporal Park Min Seok...
You can do whatever you want in here, no?
You bastard!